Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: California and Oregon fieldwork
  - Subseries 3: December 1993 research trip
    - Audio and video
      - Madeira, December 23, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR321; 1 sound cassette
      - Madeira Gusev, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR322; 1 sound cassette
      - C-P Masaruna, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR323; 1 sound cassette
      - Codpanne Reform Church, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR324; 1 sound cassette
    - Manuscripts
      - [California partial tape indexes], 1993, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/8)
      - [ Molokan News Bulletin ], January 1993, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/9)
      - [Oregon tape index], 1993, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/10)
      - [Woodburn and San Francisco field notes], 1993-1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
      - California, 1993, 1 color print (4x6 in.) (Box 11)
  - Subseries 4: 1995 research trip
    - Audio and video
      - San Francisco, June 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR366; 1 sound cassette
      - San Francisco, June 17, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR367; 1 sound cassette
      - San Francisco Bill Losbatev, June 17, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR368; 1 sound cassette
      - San Francisco EL, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR369; 1 sound cassette
      - Lanb. Sotrudniki Prayer, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR370; San Francisco: 1. Psalom almost a unison), 2. modern(?) psalom, 3. Revelations (Ia obratilsia); 1 sound cassette
      - Molokans San Francisco, January 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR371; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
      - San Francisco before the Fest, June 1995, 26 color negatives (35mm); 19 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH025 (Box 17, Box 14)
      - San Francisco, in preparation for the festival, 1995, 31 color prints (4x6 in.); 3 color prints (3.5x5 in.) (Box 11)
      - San Francisco Molokans, 1995, 14 color prints (4x6 in.) (Box 11)
- Series 4: Tula and Moscow, Russia fieldwork
  Field recordings, field notes, maps, photographs, and correspondence from Mazo's fieldwork with Molokan and Old Believer communities in Tula, Russia and Moscow, Russia.
  - Audio and video
    - A Moskva 12-16-92 Ivanovy, December 16, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR325; 1 sound cassette
    - Moskva December 92 Ivanovy Ekat. Pavl., Iv. Timof.(?), December 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR326; 1 sound cassette
    - 2 Moskva 12-16-92 Ivanovy nalozhenie Chern'(?) 12-18-9 Tul'sk. Obl. Slobodka(?), December 16, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR327; A Psalom Shchetinkin(?); 1 sound cassette
    - 3 Chern' 12-19-92 Tul'sk., December 19, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR328; 1 sound cassette
    - Chern'.,Gostinitsa Spartak. Gostinitsa 4, December 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR329; 1 sound cassette
    - 5A Chern'. Slobodka 12-20-92 Spartak, December 20, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR330; 1 sound cassette
    - A 6 Chern', Slobodka, December 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR331; 1 sound cassette
    - 7A Slobodka, chern', December 20, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR332; A Golubi/Shchetinkin; 1 sound cassette
    - Slobodka 9-18-94 1, September 14, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR333; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Slobodka 9- Z, September 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR334; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Slobodka 3, September 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR335; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Tula, September 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR336; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Tikuna, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR337; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula Chern, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR338; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR339; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR340; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR341; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR342; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR343; 1 sound cassette
    - Khil'meni(?) (?)klitopol'sk. r-i(?) Astrakhavskii.. .Simina(?) 8A (?) 1, 1994, AFC 2022/003: SR344; 1 sound cassette
    - Tula (Azerbajan), December 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR345; 1 sound cassette
    - Stedfast Tula, December 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR346; 1. Ustei Gospels (text is not in the Bible), 2. Kak lana zhelalt. Steadfast from Stavropol previously transcribed.; 1 sound cassette
    - Comparison of Psalms, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR347; 1 sound cassette
    - Molokan - Tula, 1992, AFC 2022/003: MV013; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: MV014; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Tula, 1994, AFC 2022/003: MV015; 1 video cassette (VHS)
  - Manuscripts
    - David Uraine, 1991, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Kaluga, 1994, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Moscow - Tula, 1992, See also AFC 2022/003: PH030; 1 folder of manuscript materials; 6 color prints (3.5x5 in.) (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Moscow trip 1, 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Moscow 2, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Tula, 1994, See also AFC 2022/003: PH031; 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Tula and Kaluga [maps], 1994, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Tula and Moscow field notes, December 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Tula and Moscow tape indexes and transcripts, 1992-1993, 2008-2018, afc2022003_dc001; Partial tape indexes and song transcripts from Mazo's research in Tula and Moscow, Russia between 1992 and 1994. These indexes and transcripts were a work in progress, that Mazo continued to revise and enhance throughout her career.; 5 digital manuscripts (RTF, WPD, DOCX)
  - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
    - [Doing fieldwork at a village in Northern Russia photo], undated, Photo printed on foam board.; 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 4/13)
    - [Herathbr(?) msypobe(?)], undated, Title was transcribed from Mazo's original label, spelling may be incorrect.; 2 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH019 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Moscow 87, 1987, 35 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH020 (Box 17)
    - Moscow - Tula, 1992, 26 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH030 (Box 17)
    - Tula, 1994, 82 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH031 (Box 17)
    - Village Vereschchagino O.B. central Russia, July 1994, 38 color negatives (35mm); 20 color prints (4x6 in.); AFC 2022/003: PH021 (Box 17, Box 14)
- Series 5: Poland fieldwork
  Field recordings, field notes, and correspondence from Mazo's fieldwork with Molokan and Old Believer communities in Poland.
  - Audio and video
    - 9-9-92 Stechanovic Sgimmets Otets Aposhnarii(?), September 9, 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR348; Pokrovsky Sgimmets (beginning) Sgimmets (cont.) Otets Apomenarii(?); 1 sound cassette
    - Sent. 1992 Poland Staroobriadtsy(?) Shchapov. Steinke, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR349; Shchapov Steinke (beginn). Steinke (cont.) Vroon.; 1 sound cassette
    - Sent. 1992. Poland. Staroobriadtsy Chalin. Demkova(?) Manaenkova, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR350; Chalin Demkova Manaenkova (begin) Manaenkova (cont.) Alexeev + Dergacheva(?)-(?); 1 sound cassette
    - 1992 Poland. Staroobriadtsy 4, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR351; 1 sound cassette
    - Poland-92 Staroobriadtsy Folk(?), September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR352; 1 sound cassette
    - [Untitled], September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR353; Khrychov V kostele Gabovy Grondy Gabovy Groudy; 1 sound cassette
    - Poland spiritual verses, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR354; 1 sound cassette
    - Poland, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR355; 1 sound cassette
    - Poland, September 1992, AFC 2022/003: SR356; 1 sound cassette
  - Manuscripts
    - Poland, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/2)
- Series 6: Erie, Pennsylvania fieldwork
  Field recordings, tape indexes, and field notes from Mazo's fieldwork with United States diasporic Molokan and Old Believer communities in Erie, Pennsylvania.
  - Audio and video
    - Erie verses, January 21, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR357; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Erie, January 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR358; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Dorothy Panamareff, January 21, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR359; 1 sound cassette
    - Erie Ebgonual (Anlov) Orlov, January 21, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR360; 1 sound cassette
    - Sunday liturgy, January 22, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR361; 1 sound cassette
    - Father Pimen, January 22, 1995, AFC 2022/003: SR362; 1 sound cassette
    - Prime liturgy - Old Russian rite, Church of the Nativity, November 20, 1983, AFC 2022/003: SR363; 1 sound cassette
    - Erie 4:30, October 17, 1998, AFC 2022/003: SR364; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Erie 7:00, October 17, 1998, AFC 2022/003: SR365; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
  - Manuscripts
    - [Erie tape index], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Erie tape indexes, 2004, 2018, afc2022003_dc001; Partial tape indexes from Mazo's research in Erie, Pennsylvania in 1995. These indexes were a work in progress, that Mazo continued to revise and enhance throughout her career.; 2 digital manuscripts (WPD, DOCX)
    - Erie, PA field notes, January 20-23, 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/4)
- Series 7: Mirovaya Festival, Russia
  Video recordings of the Mirovaya Folk Arts Festival in Russia.
  - Audio and video
    - Mirovaya Derevnya - Tape 1, Pt. 1; Tape 1, Pt. 2 (1st 1/2), undated, AFC 2022/003: MV016; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Mirovaya Derevnya - Tape 1, Pt. 2 (2nd 1/2); Tape 2, Pt. 1 (1st 1/2), undated, AFC 2022/003: MV017; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Mirovaya Derevnya - Tape 2, Pt. 1 (last 90 min.); Tape 2, Pt. 2 (30 min.), undated, AFC 2022/003: MV018; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Mirovaya Derevnya - Tape 3, Pt. 1 (All), undated, AFC 2022/003: MV019; 1 video cassette (VHS)
    - Mirovaya Derevnya - Tape 3, Pt. 2, undated, AFC 2022/003: MV020; 1 video cassette (VHS)
  - Manuscripts
    - [Mirovaya tape index], undated, Tape index for the video recordings of the Mirovaya Festival.; 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/5)
- Series 8: Academic files
  - Subseries 1: Molokan research files
    Research materials collected by Margarita Mazo related to Molokan communities.
    - Audio and video
      - California heartland tapes Molokans, 1975, AFC 2022/033: MV021; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Molokan songs, undated, AFC 2022/033: MV022; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - Stavropol' Koia(?) Portret kazakov - (?)kraso(?), undated, AFC 2022/033: MV023; 1 video cassette (VHS)
      - San Francisco Molokan Youth Spevka, December 1981, AFC 2022/003: SR394; 1 sound cassette
    - Manuscripts
      Photocopies of secondary source articles in both Russian and English, prayer books, and music transcriptions created by Mazo, all used to conduct general research on Molokan communities in the United States and Eastern Europe.
      - The 1980 Molokan Directory, 1980, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Boxhiĭ Plan Spaseniia: Obshchestvo Rasprostraneniia Biblii Karmannogo Formata, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Examples - Molokan music for article, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/8)
      - The Hieroglyphics of Mystery and Meaning, James J. Samarin, 1975, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Intro WWC, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/10)
      - [Medvedeva Nekrasovtry], 1985, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/11)
      - [Molokan articles in Russian], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Molokan letters, 1990-1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials; 3 color prints (4x6 in.) (Box-folder 6/1)
      - [Molokan music transcripts](1 of 3), 1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/2)
      - [Molokan music transcripts](2 of 3), 1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/3)
      - [Molokan music transcripts](3 of 3), 1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/4)
      - [Molokan newsletters], 1991-1996, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/5)
      - [Molokan research notes], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Molokans, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Molokans, 1989-1999, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/8)
      - [Molokan song analysis], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/9)
      - [Molokan song transcriptions], 1989, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/10)
      - [Moore introduction], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Moore, Molokan Oral Tradition, 1973, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/12)
      - [Music transcriptions], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/OS 2)
      - [Music transcriptions], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 19/OS 3)
      - [Music transcriptions], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 19/OS 4)
      - Nekrasovtsky record, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Nekrasovty - Tumilevich, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/14)
      - [Preobrazhenskii article photocopy], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/1)
      - [Questionnaires on the subject of the Russian language among the Molokans of the United States], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/4)
      - [Samarin article, Russian Spiritual Christianity (Molokanism) ], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/2)
      - [Sbonik Slatei article], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Smolensky [photocopies], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Sobranie, 1990, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/5)
      - [Song card catalog in Russian], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/6)
      - [Song transcriptions], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/7)
      - [Song transcriptions], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/5)
      - [Song translations], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/8)
      - [ The Subbotniki, William Aldacushion], 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/9)
      - The Summary of Dogmas and Prayer Book, 1982, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Tumilevich and others hist. sources, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/11)
      - [Velichkina article, Two Weddings in Molokan Tradition ], 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Subseries 2: Old Believers research files
    Research materials collected by Margarita Mazo related to Old Believer communities.
    - Audio and video
      - A. Sepoch(?) 1 Vereshchachinskii, August 29, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR384; 1 sound cassette
      - Perm - Vereshchachinskii r-n selo Sepoch, August 29, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR385; 1 sound cassette
      - Kulizeni, August 29, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR386; 1 sound cassette
      - Kulizeni Sivsk. s/s, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR387; 1 sound cassette
      - Vereshchachino, August 30, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR388; 1 sound cassette
      - Vereshchachino Otets Valerii End, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR389; 1 sound cassette
      - Sluzhba v Beloregenske Krasnodar. Kr. Kimeny(?), undated, AFC 2022/003: SR390; 1 sound cassette
      - Dukhovn. Stikhi, lestvitsa Kimeny(?), undated, AFC 2022/003: SR391; 1 sound cassette
      - Komi tape given by A. Vlasov Ust Tsilma spiritual verses, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR392; Syktyvkar ul. Starovskogo d. 24 k. 6b sl. Oktiabrskii kr. 55. pnil. T. 3-25-09 Vlasov Andrei Nikolaevich; 1 sound cassette
      - Sluzhba Troitsk. Kumskaia dol. Poz(?)eska, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR393; 1 sound cassette
    - Manuscripts
      Correspondence, photocopies of secondary source articles in both Russian and English, and Mazo's reading notes, all used to conduct general research on Old Believer communities in the United States and Eastern Europe.
      - [Correspondence], 1985, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Holdeman, 1997, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/2)
      - [ The Making of the Soviet System, Moshe Lewin], 1985, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Old Believers, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Old Believers - articles, misc., 1988, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Old Believers articles and miscellany, 1983-1984, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Old Believers in USA, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Old Believers, I.S., undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/7)
      - [Old Believers reading notes], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Old Believers record/materials, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/8)
      - [ Praise Old Believers preview], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/9)
      - [ Sound Catalogue of the Music of the Old Believers in the USSR and USA ], 1986, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
      - [Carrasco photos of Old Believers], undated, 14 black-and-white prints (5x7 in.); 1 black-and-white print (6x9 in.); 18 black-and-white prints (8x10 in.); 1 color print (4x6 in.); 3 black-and-white prints (3.5x5 in.) (Box 13)
  - Subseries 3: Academic paper drafts
    Drafts of articles and other academic papers and presentations written by Margarita Mazo.
    - Amplitude study, 1993, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Article drafts and research files, 1989-2018, afc2022003_dc001; Versions and drafts of academic articles written by Mazo. Article titles include: "'We Sing as We Live:' Molokans in Russia and United States," "The Verbal and the Musical in Molokans' Life," "Singing as Experience Among American-Russian Molokans," "Russian Roots, American Branches," "A Report on a Joint Research Project on Molokan Communities in the Soviet Union and United States." Also includes research files about Molokan and Old Believer communities.; 22 digital manuscripts (WPD, DOCX, RTF)
    - Boulton paper, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/12)
    - [ Change as a Confirmation of Continuity as Experienced by Russian Molokans paper drafts], January 1995, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/13)
    - [Molokan article draft], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Style sheet for Smithsonian/Folkways album notes, 1991, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/15)
    - [ The Verbal and the Musical in Molokans' Life drafts], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/16)
- Series 9: Miscellany
  Research materials, correspondence, and photographs related to Mazo's other fieldwork and research areas.
  - Audio and video
    - Novgorod, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR372; 1 sound cassette
    - Kiev conservatory, March 26, 1991, AFC 2022/003: SR373; 1 sound cassette
    - [Untitled], undated, AFC 2022/003: SR374; Copy from recording in IRLI (see reel).; 1 sound cassette
    - Russian music for Dr Mazo copy from R-R, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR375; Ansambiv(?) Nozanin I pod. Upr. Tufakhon. (M. Mazo). V kontse - nebol'shoi fragment iz drugovo tsiko kairakbozi (tanets s kasman'stami(?) - kairok?); 1 sound cassette
    - [Untitled], undated, AFC 2022/003: SR376; Voronezh, 11-channel recording. 1)chastushki pod iazyke #50 from the collection 50 russkikh par. Pesen Voronezhskoi obl. Sost. Kustovskii, Gippius(?); 1 sound cassette
    - Voronezh, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR377; Voronezh 11-channel recording A ia sidela ia devka posidela. Protezhnaia(?); 1 sound cassette
    - Voronezh, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR378; Kollektsiia Tsyganskogo autentichnogo fol'klora Sobirateli A. Gessler E. Drerts(?) Obraztsy (6); 1 sound cassette
    - Tsygane (Zhenia), undated, AFC 2022/003: SR379; 1 sound cassette
    - A short taped interview about the Brides' Lament Russian Old Believer Dunia Postnikov, September 3, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR380; 1 sound cassette
    - Plekhovo Kurskaia obl. 33D-25612, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR381; Side A: Songs of Semeiskie from Zaboikale #1-5, Songs of Cossacks from the Volgograd area #6-9; Side B: Continuation of A: II #10-12.; 1 sound cassette
    - 1. Semeiskie 2. Volgograd 3. Cossacks, undated, AFC 2022/003: SR382; 1 sound cassette
    - Novgorod Markovo/Chukotke, 1993, AFC 2022/003: SR383; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
  - Manuscripts
    - [Correspondence], 1991, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 9/8)
    - [Manuscripts accompanying SR377], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/17)
    - [Tape index accompanying dc005], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/18)
    - [Tape index by song], undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Negatives, slides, and photographic prints
    - Georgia, 1988, 26 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH044_001 - PH044_026 (Box 16)
    - Kiev, 1990, 53 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH045_001 - PH045_053 (Box 16)
    - Mocabe-L-G, 1988, 13 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH026 (Box 17)
    - Nekrasovka, 1989, 39 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH046_001 - PH046_039 (Box 16)
    - Nekrasovka, undated, 10 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH047_001 - PH047_010 (Box 16)
    - Soviet/Russian ethnomusicologists, undated, 1 color print (3.5x5 in.); 4 color prints (8x10 in.); 4 black-and-white prints (8x10 in.) (Box 12)
    - [Ukraine], undated, 23 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH048_001 - PH048_023 (Box 16)
    - [Ukraine overexposed], undated, 21 color slides (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH049_001 - PH049_021 (Box 16)
    - Untitled, undated, 14 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2022/003: PH027 (Box 17)
- Electronic media, Floppy disk containing digital files described in the container list.; 1 floppy disk (3.5 in.) (Box-folder 8/21)
Appendix A: Tape Original ID Concordance
Concordance matching Mazo's original tape ID numbers with the AFC assigned SR numbers. Mazo's numbering system was inconsistent and often has duplicate tape IDs. As a result, Sara Ludewig assigned each tape an AFC SR number. Mazo's tape indexes and field notes often contain references to the original tape ID numbers. This concordance can be used to match the new SR number with Mazo's original ID number. Tapes that appear in this list with no value in the Mazo's ID Number column did not have an original ID number.
AFC 2022/003: SR001
AFC 2022/003: SR002
AFC 2022/003: SR003
AFC 2022/003: SR004
AFC 2022/003: SR005
AFC 2022/003: SR006
AFC 2022/003: SR007
AFC 2022/003: SR008
AFC 2022/003: SR009
AFC 2022/003: SR010 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR011 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR012 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR013 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR014 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR015 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR016 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR017 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR018 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR019 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR020 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR021 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR022 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR023 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR024 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR025 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR026 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR027 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR028 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR029 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR030 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR031 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR032 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR033 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR034 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR035 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR036 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR037 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR038 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR039 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR040 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR041 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR042 Tape 5
AFC 2022/003: SR043 1
AFC 2022/003: SR044 2
AFC 2022/003: SR045 3
AFC 2022/003: SR046 4
AFC 2022/003: SR047 5
AFC 2022/003: SR048 6
AFC 2022/003: SR049 7
AFC 2022/003: SR050 8
AFC 2022/003: SR051
AFC 2022/003: SR052 1
AFC 2022/003: SR053 2
AFC 2022/003: SR054 3